http://www.nationalprecision.com/legal/

Product
Miniature BearingsAerospace BearingsStaking ToolSilverthin BearingsNeedle Roller BearingsSpherical Plain BearingsBushingsBall Bearings
Mechatronics Privacy Policy
Mechatronics prides itself on a commitment to privacy and respect for the user
experience. We are updating Mechatronics's Privacy Policy with options that give
the users better control of their privacy and greater security for their data.
In summary, here's what this means to you:
We've re-organized our Privacy Policy to make it clearer and more understandable
including information on what data we collect, how we use it, and the rights that
are available to you. Our updates and changes will make it easier for you to control
the information you provide us. You'll see that our policy explains your choices
about this.
We're preparing for the EU's General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This
means new requirements as to how we process EU personal data. As a result, we're
updating our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use to better explain our relationship
with our users and how we keep your personal information safe.
In detail, you can read on. You'll find specific information relating to the data
we collect and what we do with it, as well as specific information relating to tools
available to you to manage your data up to, and including,
removing it from our website.
Mechatronics Cookie Information
What we collect.
Mechatronics does not collect much data: we use Google analytics and advertising; we allow
users to contact us via forms; and we sometimes email users who have requested news updates
from us. Mechatronics does not share your data with third parties. Here is what we do
specifically and how you can control it: Read More
Mechatronics Opt Out
The following form allows you to Opt Out of Mechatronics commercial email communication:
SIGN UP
Mechatronics use cookies to personalize content and ads and also to analyse our traffic. For more information, see our Privacy and Legal Notices including tools to opt out.
